<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Root>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;Kirchen Bell. This is the town we live in.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yes. It's not very big, but... I think it's a peaceful town that's easy to live in.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;I really love this town, too!&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="2" icon2="-1" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;The Forest of Fairies... I wonder if fairies really exist...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;I heard that humans with impure hearts can't see them.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;O-oh, right! Now that I think about it, I saw a fairy the other day! I just forgot, ahaha...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="2" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This garden is a mess, but it's pretty because of all the flowers blooming.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yeah. Not many people visit, so a lot of the plants growing here are shy around people.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="3" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;People say that if you go here early in the morning, you can find all kinds of things washed up on the shore.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Uu... Early in the morning, huh... I'm really not good at waking up early...&quot;" icon0="2" icon1="-1" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is a really deep canyon... I looked down the edge of a cliff before, but I couldn't see the bottom at all...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;The footing isn't very stable either, so be careful.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="-1" icon3="2" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;...I don't like this place.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yeah. There are lots of graves here. If you go at night, there could be lots of ghosts...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;S-stop that! I don't want to think about it!&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="2" icon2="-1" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;...This palace is all upside down and inverted. I wonder why it's like this?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Maybe someone with strange taste built it like this to surprise other people.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="3" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;Hmm, this place doesn't seem like a part of this world...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Very sharp. This place is actually...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;If you're going to say it's the netherworld, I don't want to know!&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="17" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;What could be sealed here...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Maybe a super big, strong Puni?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;No, it's probably a evil spirit...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Well, we know good things are never sealed away.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="3" icon2="2" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This lake is wondrous and beautiful...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;This would be fun to swim in!&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;The water's good, so I like it!&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;People sure think differently.&quot;" icon0="2" icon1="0" icon2="3" icon3="2" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This was formerly my atelier.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;That's unfair! It's so big, my atelier doesn't even compare! That's so unfair, Plachta!&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;I-I'm not really sure how to respond...&quot;" icon0="17" icon1="0" icon2="-1" icon3="17" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This road was made for people making pilgrimages to the church. There are cabins to rest in, too.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;There aren't a huge number of people making pilgrimages, so it's a little unmaintained...&quot;" icon0="2" icon1="-1" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This farm has a big wheat field.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;...Is it really okay to take the wheat?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;The farmers are really nice, and say it's okay to take what we need. We should thank them sometime.&quot;" icon0="2" icon1="0" icon2="2" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This place has a pretty flower bed!&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;The soil quality here is good, and it gets lots of sun. The flowers say it's like heaven.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yeah. It makes me want to sun bathe and take a nap.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="3" icon2="-1" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;What's the cabin here for?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;It's a place to leave logs from lumbering.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Huh... It seems like a lot of work to carry lumber from here to town...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="2" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is a large group of ruins spread out on a field.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Hmm, I wonder what this place was in the past?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Judging from the shape of the pillars... A temple? Something could have been enshrined here.&quot;" icon0="2" icon1="0" icon2="2" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is a forest near the town. The monsters that appear aren't very strong, so it's great for gathering.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;That reminds me, we all came here to play when we were kids, then got scolded for leaving the town...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="2" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;The trees grow thinly in this forest. It's called the Blessed Forest because it blesses us with such bounty... It's a pretty straightforward name.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Isn't it good to have an easy to understand name?&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="-1" icon3="2" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is a shallow forest with some openings...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yeah. You can pick good fruit here, so the townsfolk come here to gather them once in a while. It's like a place for some relaxation.&quot;" icon0="17" icon1="0" icon2="-1" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This forest is kind of humid. I wonder if the mushrooms growing here are edible?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Even I'm not very familiar with mushrooms. It would probably be best not to try them.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="3" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;Enlightened...? That's a pretty amazing name.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Apparently, long ago, a certain sage came here to train, and achieved enlightenment.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Huh, maybe I should try training too.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="2" icon2="-1" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;These ruins have decayed completely, and have been overgrown by trees.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Huh, you can even see the roots covering them in some places... I wonder what era this is from?&quot;" icon0="17" icon1="-1" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is an open area inside a forest.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;That's right. I asked the plants, and they said some fierce animals have claimed it as their territory.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;I see... We need to be careful, then...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="3" icon2="-1" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is a forest near a rocky area.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yeah. I didn't think trees could grow in a place like this.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Don't underestimate the power of trees. They're amazing, they can take root anywhere.&quot;" icon0="3" icon1="0" icon2="3" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;It's dark because of all the trees growing, and everything looks the same. It seems easy to get lost here.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;You need to advance slowly while leaving markers... I don't want to ever end up stranded.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="2" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;There are two trees here with intertwined branches, like they're holding hands.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;...I see. I thought they were just normal trees, but now that you mention it, I can see what you mean...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="17" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;These ruins are near a river.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Despite the long passage of time, it's resisted the river's erosion, and still remains. It must have originally been a very strong building.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="17" icon2="-1" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This forest always has really thick fog, so you can barely see ahead of you.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;The plants are sad that they don't get enough light because of the fog, too. It makes me feel bad...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="3" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This place is like a little spring. The main sights are the three bridges all lined up.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;So that's why it's called the Three Bridge Springs.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yeah. It's kind of a famous place.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="17" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is the shore of a lake. I wonder if you could go to the little island you can see nearby?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;You could swim there, but... Is there really a reason to go?&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="3" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is a really quiet lake. The only things you hear are the sound of water, rustling leaves, and the cries of monsters...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Wait... Is that really quiet?&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="-1" icon3="3" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;Apparently this is a famous place to fish. If you cast a line, fish will bite almost instantly.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Huh... I've never gone fishing before. Maybe I should try it sometime...&quot;" icon0="2" icon1="-1" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;There's a small island in the middle of the pond. There's a bridge, so you can walk over to it.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;It's a really small island, so try not to slip.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="-1" icon3="2" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This place has lots of rough rocks.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yes, there are many hiding places, so be careful for surprise attacks.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;I don't think hide and seek would ever end here...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="2" icon2="-1" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This hill has abundant vegetation. The slope is pretty steep, so you need to be careful while walking.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yeah. But it's such a nice hill... It makes me want to run down at full speed...&quot;" icon0="2" icon1="-1" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This slope leads up a mountain. It seems to be right at the border of different climates.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;It has green grass, and white sand... It's a little strange to see it so neatly divided...&quot;" icon0="17" icon1="-1" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This is a sandy valley. The dying trees stand out, and it's sad to see them...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;...It's a harsh place with barren soil. I'd like to transplant them, if I could...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="-1" icon2="3" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;This place has lots of bones...&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yes. It got its name from the rows of bones standing out, almost like a forest.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Uu... I don't want to go here at night...&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="17" icon2="-1" icon3="0" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;These are ruins near the waterside... Right?&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Yes... Ruins are very valuable. The study of how people lived in the past is very useful to us.&quot;" icon0="0" icon1="17" icon2="-1" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
    <LibraryMap note="&quot;It's said that this place was once a grand city.&quot;&lt;CR&gt;&quot;Huh. So people were living here in the past... I wonder why it ended up like this?&quot;" icon0="17" icon1="-1" icon2="0" icon3="-1" permit="true"/>
</Root>
