<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Root>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Container &amp; Basket" memo="★Exploration: Container &amp; Basket" img0="2" img1="3" img2="4" text0="Materials obtained in town and in the field will be placed in the &lt;CLGR&gt;Container&lt;CLNR&gt; and &lt;CLGR&gt;Basket&lt;CLNR&gt;, respectively. Items in the Basket will automatically be sent to the Container when returning to town." text1="There's a limit to how much can fit in the Container and Basket. However, the limit on the Basket can be increased by equipping a certain item." text2="If you exceed your Basket's maximum capacity in the field, you will have to either throw the items away, or swap them with other items in your Basket. Be careful." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Town Map" memo="★Exploration: Town Map" startEv="EVENT_MS09_020" img0="79" img1="79" img2="80" img3="80" text0="While in town, you can press &lt;IM11&gt; to open the &lt;CLGR&gt;Town Map&lt;CLNR&gt;." text1="You can select destinations to travel to in the Town Map. You can also see what characters are present in each area." text2="Sometimes, you will find characters in unexpected places." text3="When characters aren't in their normal places, open the Town Map and look for them. You might be able to hear something different from them." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Gathering" memo="★Exploration: Gathering" startEv="EVENT_MM01_130" img0="5" img1="44" img2="44" text0="In the field, if you press &lt;IM00&gt; near &lt;CLGR&gt;Gathering Points&lt;CLNR&gt;, you can gather items." text1="Touching monsters in the field will start a battle. Hitting monsters with a &lt;CLGR&gt;Swing&lt;CLNR&gt; will let you start the battle with an advantage." text2="You can Swing by pressing &lt;IM04&gt;. Make good use of this." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Gathering Level" memo="★Exploration: Gathering Level" startEv="EVENT_MM01_160" img0="7" img1="8" img2="9" text0="Gathering in the field will cause new monsters to appear. Defeating monsters causes new Gathering Points to appear." text1="Continuing to explore the same field will cause &lt;CLGR&gt;Gathering Level&lt;CLNR&gt; to increase. Higher Gathering Level allows you to find better materials." text2="However, as Gathering Level increases, monsters will also grow stronger, so be careful." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Time &amp; Day" memo="★Exploration: Time &amp; Day" startEv="EVENT_MS07_050" img0="10" img1="11" img2="12" img3="13" text0="Moving on the World Map, gathering, fighting, and performing Synthesis all cause time to pass. The passage of time can cause changes to the field." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Time&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;There are 4 times of day: morning, day, evening, and night. The time of day changes the situation of the town, gatherable items, and monsters that appear." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Weather&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Weather includes clouds, rain, and thunderstorms. Some monsters and gatherable materials can only be found during certain weather." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;3.Day&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;There are 5 days in a week: Sprout, Bud, Flower, Fruit, and Seed. The day of the week can affect Request and Rumor updates, as well as affect story progress." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Friend Level" memo="★Exploration: Friend Level" startEv="EVENT_MS09_020" img0="105" img1="106" img2="106" text0="All party characters except Sophie have a &lt;CLGR&gt;Friend Level&lt;CLNR&gt;, representing how close they are to her. Increasing the &lt;CLGR&gt;Friend Level&lt;CLNR&gt; causes that character's story to progress." text1="Friend Level can be increased by adventuring together, completing specific Requests, and more, but there's a limit to progress. If the limit is reached, the number will turn red." text2="The Friend Level limit can be unlocked by progressing that character's story. You should talk to them often once a limit is reached." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Visit Town Often" memo="★Exploration: Visit Town Often" startEv="EVENT_MS09_020" img0="75" img1="76" text0="Gathering, combat, and alchemy studies are important, but don't forget to interact with the townsfolk. While they're usually busy with their lives, sometimes you might find them doing something different." text1="Having silly chats with the townsfolk, or solving their problems, will slowly cause them to grow closer." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Recipe Ideas" memo="★Exploration: Recipe Ideas" startEv="EVENT_MS05_030" img0="14" img1="15" text0="Sophie can come up with ideas for item recipes through exploration, Synthesis, combat, and other actions." text1="You can check conditions to come up with recipes from Recipe Ideas in the Main Menu. You will also see progress until the next recipe relating to Plachta's memories." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Exploration Equipment" memo="★Exploration: Exploration Equipment" startEv="EVENT_MS06_020" img0="16" img1="17" text0="By equipping exploration items, Sophie can increase her Basket capacity, increase the number of materials she gathers, and more." text1="You can carry up to 5 exploration items. Equip items relating to the tasks you wish to complete to make your gathering trips more efficient." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Presents" memo="★Exploration: Presents" startEv="EVENT_MS05_120" img0="18" img1="19" text0="You can give a present to a character by approaching them and pressing &lt;IM04&gt;. You won't be able to give them another present for a while afterwards." text1="However, each character has items that they like and dislike. The item you give will affect their Friend Level appropriately." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: LP" memo="★Exploration: LP" startEv="EVENT_MM01_160" img0="20" img1="21" text0="LP represents stamina necessary for exploration. Moving on the World Map, gathering, and combat all consume this, and all stats will be reduced when it falls below certain points." text1="LP can be restored mainly through eating food. You should bring a lot when traveling to distant areas." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Exploration: Clip" memo="★Exploration: Clip" startEv="EVENT_MS05_110" img0="108" img1="109" img2="110" text0="In the reference book submenu, you can Clip information that you would like to record." text1="You can press &lt;IM15&gt; in the field to bring up a list of Clipped info, and jump directly to the recorded entry by selecting it." text2="If the recorded entry is a Synthesis item, you can Synthesize from a Clip while in the atelier. A Clip icon will also display in the recipe list." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Synthesis Basics" memo="★Synthesis: Synthesis Basics" startEv="EVENT_MM01_070" img0="22" img1="23" img2="24" text0="You can perform Synthesis and create items by approaching the cauldron in the atelier and pressing &lt;IM00&gt;." text1="To Synthesize items, you need to have all the materials specified by the recipe. If you don't have enough, obtain them by gathering in the field, or buying in town." text2="If a recipe's level is higher than Sophie's alchemy level, quality will be decreased proportional to the level difference. If you perform Synthesis with too low quality, it will result in failure, so be aware of this." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Flow of Synthesis" memo="★Synthesis: Flow of Synthesis" startEv="EVENT_MS05_030" img0="22" img1="33" img2="34" img3="35" img4="36" text0="Synthesis is split into 4 parts: Material selection, cauldron selection, material placement, and trait transfer." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Material Selection&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt; Select the materials for the recipe from the Container. The average size of the selected materials will be the size of the Synthesized item." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Cauldron Selection&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Choose one cauldron you currently possess. Different cauldrons can result in different bonuses and panel sizes." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;3.Material Placement&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Place the selected materials in the cauldron. Quality will increase with more panels covered, while Effect Value will grow with bonuses obtained." text4="&lt;CLGR&gt;4.Trait Transfer&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Select the traits from the materials to transfer. The number of traits you can transfer increases with alchemy level." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Categories" memo="★Synthesis: Categories" startEv="EVENT_MS05_030" img0="25" img1="26" img2="27" text0="All materials have a &lt;CLGR&gt;Category&lt;CLNR&gt; broadly representing its type, as well as a &lt;CLGR&gt;Category Value&lt;CLNR&gt; representing its affinity for that category." text1="For example, if the recipe specifies a category like (Plant), then any material from that category can be selected as a material." text2="Even among the same category, materials with higher category value can cause more powerful effects to appear." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Effects &amp; Effect Value" memo="★Synthesis: Effects &amp; Effect Value" startEv="EVENT_MS05_030" img0="28" img1="29" img2="81" text0="&lt;CLGR&gt;Effects&lt;CLNR&gt; are unique abilities of each item. For instance, the &quot;Uni Bag&quot; has effects like &quot;Physical Damage S&quot;." text1="During Synthesis, the effect that appears will be set by the &lt;CLGR&gt;Effect Value&lt;CLNR&gt;. The initial Effect Value is the total Category Value of the selected materials." text2="Effect Value can be increased by obtaining the bonuses that appear on the panels." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Traits" memo="★Synthesis: Traits" startEv="EVENT_MS09_030" img0="30" img1="36" text0="&lt;CLGR&gt;Traits&lt;CLNR&gt; are the hidden power in each item. They are split into 2 broad types: traits that enhance the item's abilities, and traits that add new ones to the item." text1="Traits can be transferred during Synthesis. You can also combine some traits to create higher level traits." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Cauldron Effects" memo="★Synthesis: Cauldron Effects" startEv="EVENT_MS05_050" img0="37" img1="38" img2="39" img3="40" img4="41" text0="Cauldrons have special effects that influence Synthesis. Rebuilding a cauldron can improve those effects." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Unique Effect&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Alchemy cauldrons have unique effects. For example, you won't fail with low quality, or enhance bonuses that are the same color as the liquid in the cauldron." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Material Manipulation&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Allows you to flip materials horizontally, vertically, or rotate them when placing." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;3.Bonus Display&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Higher level will cause more bonuses to appear at the start of Synthesis." text4="&lt;CLGR&gt;4.Panel Size&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Makes the panel size bigger. The maximum panel size is 6x6." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Special Panels" memo="★Synthesis: Special Panels" startEv="EVENT_MS05_030" img0="96" img1="97" img2="98" text0="Each recipe has different placement of colors on panels. Certain recipes also have unique shapes, with holes where some panels should be." text1="Materials cannot be placed where there are holes, so large materials might not be optimal to create the best items." text2="Stronger items will have more complex panel shapes. Select the most optimal materials for the panel shape you're dealing with." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Synthesis: Useful Functions" memo="★Synthesis: Useful Functions" startEv="EVENT_MS05_030" img0="99" img1="100" img2="101" img3="102" text0="Synthesis has 3 useful functions while placing materials. This is an introduction to these functions." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Item Info Display&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;By pressing &lt;IM04&gt;, you can show information for the item under the cursor. Pressing &lt;IM04&gt; again will hide it." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Material Swap&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Pressing &lt;IM11&gt; lets you swap the material under the cursor with a different one." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;3.Cauldron, Trait Transfer Check&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Pressing &lt;IM15&gt; lets you check the cauldron and traits that are available. You can then press &lt;IM11&gt;&lt;IM15&gt; to change the information displayed." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Battle Basics" memo="★Battle: Battle Basics" startEv="EVENT_MM01_120" img0="45" img1="83" img2="84" text0="During battle, all enemy and ally actions will be performed at once each turn." text1="After enemy actions are determined, you can select actions for allies. Actions can be selected through commands. Choose the action to perform, then press &lt;IM00&gt;." text2="The turn order of enemies and allies is shown on the left, and go from top to bottom. This order can be affected by different actions performed." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Monster Actions" memo="★Battle: Monster Actions" startEv="EVENT_MM01_120" img0="46" img1="47" img2="48" img3="85" text0="Monster actions are split into 3 types: &lt;CLGR&gt;Attack&lt;CLNR&gt;, &lt;CLGR&gt;Skill&lt;CLNR&gt;, and &lt;CLGR&gt;Warning&lt;CLNR&gt;." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Attack&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;The monster will use a normal attack." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Skill&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;The monster will use a skill, which can result in various actions." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;3.Warning&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;The flame on the bottom right of the time card will burn, and the monster will use a powerful skill. Be very careful when the flame grows large." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Stances" memo="★Battle: Stances" startEv="EVENT_MM01_120" img0="49" img1="50" img2="51" img3="86" img4="84" text0="One important factor in battle is &quot;Stance&quot;. There are &quot;Offense&quot; and &quot;Defense&quot; stances, and they can be changed by pressing &lt;IM11&gt;&lt;IM15&gt;." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Offense Stance&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Increases attack power, and allows allies to use additional attack support actions, &lt;CLGR&gt;&quot;Support Attacks&quot;&lt;CLNR&gt;." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Defense Stance&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Increases defense, and also allows allies to use the support action &lt;CLGR&gt;&quot;Support Guard&quot;&lt;CLNR&gt;, shielding allies who are being attacked." text3="&quot;Support Attack&quot; and &quot;Support Guard&quot; will automatically be used when the Chain Link reaches 100%." text4="You can gain an advantage in battle by making use of enemy action order and forecasts, and swapping stances accordingly. Make good use of the information provided." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Multi Support" memo="★Battle: Multi Support" startEv="EVENT_MS05_080" img0="87" img1="88" img2="89" img3="90" img4="90" text0="A powerful support action called &lt;CLGR&gt;Multi Support&lt;CLNR&gt; can be used when 2 or more allies are in the same Stance." text1="Multi Support will automatically activate when the Chain Link Gauge is &lt;CLGR&gt;200%&lt;CLNR&gt; or higher, and 2 or more allies in the same Stance have finished their turns." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Offense Act&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;After fulfilling conditions in &quot;Offense&quot; stance, a powerful chain attack &quot;Offense Act&quot; will activate." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Defense Act&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;After fulfilling conditions in &quot;Defense&quot; stance, a powerful chain guard &quot;Defense Act&quot; will activate." text4="Each Multi Support effect differs between characters. Try using them with all kinds of characters, and see what you like best." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Special Support" memo="★Battle: Special Support" startEv="EVENT_MS05_090" img0="91" img1="92" img2="93" img3="94" img4="95" text0="The strongest support action, called &lt;CLGR&gt;Special Support&lt;CLNR&gt;, can be used when 3 or more allies are in the same Stance." text1="Special Support will automatically activate when the Chain Link Gauge is &lt;CLGR&gt;300%&lt;CLNR&gt; or higher, and 3 or more allies in the same Stance have finished their turns." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Special Attack&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;After fulfilling conditions in &quot;Offense&quot; stance, a powerful chain attack &quot;Special Attack&quot; will activate." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Special Guard&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;After fulfilling conditions in &quot;Defense&quot; stance, a powerful chain guard &quot;Special Guard&quot; will activate." text4="Special Support abilities are extremely powerful, but they also consume a large amount of the Chain Link Gauge. Choose your timing wisely." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Usable Items" memo="★Battle: Usable Items" startEv="EVENT_MM01_100" img0="52" img1="53" text0="Items created through Synthesis can be equipped for use during battle." text1="As the alchemist, Sophie has infinite cost, but other party members can only equip specific items that fit within their cost limits." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Resistances" memo="★Battle: Resistances" startEv="EVENT_MM01_120" img0="103" img1="103" img2="104" text0="Skill and item attacks can have &lt;CLGR&gt;physical&lt;CLNR&gt;, &lt;CLGR&gt;magic&lt;CLNR&gt;, &lt;CLGR&gt;fire&lt;CLNR&gt;, &lt;CLGR&gt;ice&lt;CLNR&gt;, or &lt;CLGR&gt;lightning&lt;CLNR&gt; attributes, as well as &lt;CLGR&gt;non-attribute&lt;CLNR&gt;. &lt;CLGR&gt;Resistance&lt;CLNR&gt; represents how strong a character is to them." text1="Resistances have 3 levels: &lt;CLGR&gt;Weakness&lt;CLNR&gt;, &lt;CLGR&gt;Resistance&lt;CLNR&gt;, and &lt;CLGR&gt;Super Resistance&lt;CLNR&gt;. The order is &lt;CLGR&gt;Weakness ＜ No Resistance ＜ Resistance ＜ Super Resistance&lt;CLNR&gt;." text2="The resistances of characters and monsters can be checked through Status, or the Encyclopedia." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Status Ailments" memo="★Battle: Status Ailments" startEv="EVENT_MM01_120" img0="54" img1="54" img2="54" img3="54" img4="54" text0="&lt;CLGR&gt;Ailments&lt;CLNR&gt; are negative effects that can be applied during battle. Ailments can be recovered from after a number of turns, as well as the use of recovery items." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.No Action&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Cannot act due to Sleep or other effect.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Poison&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Will take damage each turn." text2="&lt;CLGR&gt;3.Slow&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Actions become slower.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;CLGR&gt;4.Curse&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Take damage when receiving healing effects." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;5.Blind&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Reduces accuracy and evasion rate.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;CLGR&gt;6.Weak&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Reduces the power of all skills." text4="&lt;CLGR&gt;7.No Heal&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Will not heal from recovery effects.&lt;CR&gt;&lt;CLGR&gt;8.Seal&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;Cannot use skills or items." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Break" memo="★Battle: Break" startEv="EVENT_MM01_120" img0="55" img1="56" img2="57" text0="Attacking the same enemy multiple times can cause a &lt;CLGR&gt;Break&lt;CLNR&gt;. While Broken, turns will be skipped, and damage will be critical when attacked." text1="Break will be removed after turns pass or by being attacked, but it can give you an enormous advantage in battle, so you should be assertive in using it." text2="However, it's also possible for allies to be Broken by enemy attacks. Swap stances and use recovery items to prevent Break from happening." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Battle: Abilities" memo="★Battle: Abilities" startEv="EVENT_MS06_010" img0="58" img1="59" text0="&lt;CLGR&gt;Abilities&lt;CLNR&gt; are a system to develop party members by spending points gained through leveling up." text1="Abilities add additional parameters, enhance or bestow combat skills, and more. You're free to distribute the points as you see fit." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Doll Making" memo="★Facility: Doll Making" startEv="EVENT_MM06_090" img0="42" img1="43" text0="Doll Making allows you to add materials to Plachta's body to change her appearance and parameters." text1="Materials used will change the values for &quot;Cute&quot;, &quot;Smart&quot;, &quot;Brave&quot;, and &quot;Mystery&quot;. These values will cause changes in Plachta's appearance and parameters." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Café" memo="★Facility: Café" startEv="EVENT_MS05_100" img0="60" img1="61" img2="107" img3="62" img4="63" text0="At the &lt;CLGR&gt;Café&lt;CLNR&gt;, you can accept &lt;CLGR&gt;Requests&lt;CLNR&gt; from Horst, and hear about &lt;CLGR&gt;Rumors&lt;CLNR&gt;. Requests and Rumors are updated after set periods of time, so be sure to check back often." text1="&lt;CLGR&gt;1.Requests&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;By solving the townsfolks' problems, you will receive money as a reward." text2="Some Requests have a time limit, and you will receive a warning when it approaches. Exceeding the time limit will reduce your rating with Horst, so be careful." text3="&lt;CLGR&gt;2.Rumors&lt;CLNR&gt;&lt;CR&gt;By paying money, you can learn about changes to gatherable materials and monsters in fields, as well as other helpful information." text4="When you accept a Request or hear a Rumor, the points on the World Map will be affected." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Church" memo="★Facility: Church" startEv="EVENT_QC09_PAM_010" img0="64" text0="At the &lt;CLGR&gt;Church&lt;CLNR&gt;, you can buy talismans, holy water, and other unique items. Money paid is considered a donation to the church. Something good might happen when this reaches a certain amount." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Trade Shop" memo="★Facility: Trade Shop" startEv="EVENT_MS05_200" img0="65" img1="66" text0="Completing certain Requests will allow you to receive &lt;CLGR&gt;Vouchers&lt;CLNR&gt; from Horst." text1="Vouchers you receive can be exchanged for various items managed by Tess. Better items require more Vouchers, so collect as many as you can by completing Requests." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Duplication Shop" memo="★Facility: Duplication Shop" startEv="EVENT_QC05_COR_040" img0="67" img1="68" img2="69" text0="At the &lt;CLGR&gt;Duplication Shop&lt;CLNR&gt;, Sophie can have the items she Synthesizes copied for purchase." text1="The price when buying an item depends on its quality, so be sure to check the price when registering an item." text2="Also, by becoming more friendly with Corneria, you will be able to register more items." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Automatic Refill" memo="★Facility: Automatic Refill" startEv="EVENT_MS05_150" img0="70" img1="77" img2="78" text0="Selecting the &lt;CLGR&gt;Auto Refill&lt;CLNR&gt; command at Corneria's shop allows you to turn this feature on and off." text1="Setting refills to &quot;On&quot; will cause items to be refilled to their full use count when you return to the atelier from the field." text2="However, if you don't have enough money, the refill won't happen, and will be set to &quot;Off&quot;. You must go back to Corneria when you wish to start refilling items again." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Weapon/Armor Crafting" memo="★Facility: Weapon/Armor Crafting" startEv="EVENT_QC08_LOG_040" img0="71" img1="72" text0="At the &lt;CLGR&gt;Blacksmith&lt;CLNR&gt; and the &lt;CLGR&gt;Clothing Shop&lt;CLNR&gt;, you can craft weapons and armor for party members." text1="Crafting weapons requires &lt;CLGR&gt;(Weapon Material)&lt;CLNR&gt;, and armor requires &lt;CLGR&gt;(Armor Material)&lt;CLNR&gt;, as well as other specified materials." permit="true"/>
    <LibraryHelp note="Facility: Weapon/Armor Enhancing" memo="★Facility: Weapon/Armor Enhancing" startEv="EVENT_QC08_LOG_070" img0="73" img1="74" text0="At the &lt;CLGR&gt;Blacksmith&lt;CLNR&gt; and the &lt;CLGR&gt;Clothing Shop&lt;CLNR&gt;, you can enhance weapons and armor using new materials to boost their stats." text1="Each item has a limited number of times that it can be enhanced. The stats that are enhanced depend on the item's quality and traits." permit="true"/>
</Root>
